{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 2, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "pups", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "pups", 
            "salience": 0.5201231
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "adoption", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "adoption", 
            "salience": 0.18378973
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "pups", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "pups", 
            "salience": 0.078079514
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "group", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "group", 
            "salience": 0.062170897
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "male", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "male", 
            "salience": 0.057842966
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "location", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "location", 
            "salience": 0.043819387
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Sg Long", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0czgc0", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bandar_Sungai_Long"
            }, 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Sg Long", 
            "salience": 0.01829517
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Kajang", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/049x3", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kajang"
            }, 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Kajang", 
            "salience": 0.01829517
        }, 
        {
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "pups", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "metadata": {}, 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "pups", 
            "salience": 0.017584061
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 1.4, 
        "score": 0.2
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "2 female pups up for adoption.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Definitely cute and smart.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.9, 
                "score": 0.9
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "group of 5 pups, 2 died, 1 male adopted, left 2 female pups , location at Sg Long， Kajang.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.4, 
                "score": -0.4
            }
        }
    ], 
    "raw_content": "2 female pups up for adoption. Definitely cute and smart. group of 5 pups, 2 died, 1 male adopted, left 2 female pups , location at Sg Long， Kajang. ", 
    "categories": []
}