{
    "Fee": 0, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "2 kittens available Cookie: male, brown and white mixed, very active and friendly BooBoo: female, black and white mixed, character is soft and friendly to people Both are 2 months-old Preferably adopt both kittens together as they are close to each other.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.6, 
                "score": 0.6
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Available for negeri sembilan and selangor area", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.1, 
                "score": 0.1
            }
        }
    ], 
    "PhotoAmt": 4.0, 
    "Breed1": 266, 
    "Breed2": 266, 
    "MaturitySize": 1, 
    "Dewormed": 1, 
    "label": 4, 
    "Color1": 1, 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.22274576, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kittens", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kittens", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.19926178, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Cookie", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "Cookie", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.19926178, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "male", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "male", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.18127564, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "people", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "people", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.06814075, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "character", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "character", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.039924603, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "each other", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "each other", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.033851326, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "BooBoo", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "BooBoo", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.02018849, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kittens", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kittens", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.013633146, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "area", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "area", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.013633146, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "selangor", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "selangor", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.008083583, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "negeri sembilan", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "negeri sembilan", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0211kz", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Negeri_Sembilan"
            }
        }
    ], 
    "Color3": 7, 
    "Color2": 2, 
    "categories": [], 
    "Gender": 3, 
    "Age": 2, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "FurLength": 1, 
    "Quantity": 2, 
    "language": "en", 
    "Vaccinated": 1, 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 0.7, 
        "score": 0.3
    }, 
    "Sterilized": 2
}