{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 4, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.40201455, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.20101684, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Arked Meranti", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Arked Meranti", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.07845728, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Universiti Teknologi Malaysia", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Universiti Teknologi Malaysia", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/05t_5s", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/University_of_Technology,_Malaysia"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.07845728, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Skudai", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Skudai", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/058z21", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Skudai"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.06390834, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "hometown", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "hometown", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.049294483, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.04511063, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.043849234, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "hostel", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "hostel", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.021142181, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "food court", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "food court", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.016749162, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "bit", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "bit", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 2.1, 
        "score": 0
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Found this poor kitten today at Arked Meranti in Universiti Teknologi Malaysia, Skudai.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.5, 
                "score": -0.5
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "I'm returning to my hometown tomorrow (1/) so I can't bring her back to my hostel.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": -0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Pls contact me at if you would like to have this cute kitten.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.4, 
                "score": 0.4
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "You might need to do a bit of searching on your own but most likely the kitten is always at the food court.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Thank you for reading!", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}