{
    "Fee": 0, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Ani and Ana was rescued and housed in a Shelter home for women for 2 years, where they provide good company and therapy.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.8, 
                "score": 0.8
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Now that the shelter home is closing down, we hope to find a good home for them.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }
    ], 
    "PhotoAmt": 3.0, 
    "Breed1": 266, 
    "Breed2": 0, 
    "MaturitySize": 2, 
    "Dewormed": 3, 
    "label": 4, 
    "Color1": 2, 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.43079668, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Ani", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Ani", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.15059394, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Ana", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Ana", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.12220165, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0679639, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "women", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "women", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.067806795, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Shelter", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Shelter", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0j62r29", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shelter_(building)"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.063280255, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "therapy", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "therapy", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.052896325, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "company", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "company", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.031624816, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0128356395, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "shelter home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "shelter home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "Color3": 7, 
    "Color2": 4, 
    "categories": [], 
    "Gender": 2, 
    "Age": 24, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "FurLength": 1, 
    "Quantity": 2, 
    "language": "en", 
    "Vaccinated": 2, 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 1, 
        "score": 0.5
    }, 
    "Sterilized": 1
}