{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 2, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.23416294, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "friend", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "friend", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.22687784, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "woman", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "woman", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.14347494, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Jinn", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Jinn", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/03dr7", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jinn"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.12471522, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kittens", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kittens", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.1060631, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kittens", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kittens", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.063837595, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "ground", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "ground", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.063837595, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "garbage dump", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "garbage dump", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.031366643, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "scolding", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "scolding", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.005664136, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Mayo Clinic Taipan", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Mayo Clinic Taipan", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 1.7, 
        "score": 0
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "My friend, Jinn, and I actually saw a woman literally throwing these kittens to the ground at a garbage dump.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": -0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "I gave her a good scolding and we rescued the kittens, now they are lodged at Mayo Clinic Taipan waiting for you to take them home to love.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": 0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Please contact me at if interested to adopt.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Thank you!", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.1, 
                "score": 0.1
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}