{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 1, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.5276971, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kittens", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kittens", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.18739617, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "street", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "street", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.06961844, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "person", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "person", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.050576087, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home owner", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "home owner", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.041398387, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "someone", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "someone", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.03643876, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "bag", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "CONSUMER_GOOD", 
            "name": "bag", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.027942805, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "someone", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "someone", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.016946621, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.013716055, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "owner", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "owner", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.010279108, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "love", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "love", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.009351416, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "cat", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "cat", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.008639092, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 2.8, 
        "score": 0
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "i found these very cute kittens on the street.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.8, 
                "score": 0.8
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "someone has dumped them in a plastic bag.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": -0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "i already found someone to adopt them but unfortunately, that person has to return back these kitten to me because his home owner doesn't allowed cat to be at home.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.5, 
                "score": -0.5
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "please adopt them, they are little and need some love from a new owner.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.6, 
                "score": 0.6
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}