{
    "Fee": 0, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Kitten is one of the 4 babies which are brought to our house by their mother, we have given out 3 brother &amp; sisters, now only left this youngest &amp; obedient baby sister, hopefully can meet her future owner soon.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.3, 
                "score": 0.3
            }
        }
    ], 
    "PhotoAmt": 5.0, 
    "Breed1": 266, 
    "Breed2": 0, 
    "MaturitySize": 2, 
    "Dewormed": 2, 
    "label": 3, 
    "Color1": 4, 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.25104967, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "babies", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "babies", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.2352836, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "one", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "one", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.22315966, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0609374, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "baby sister", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "baby sister", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.055949207, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "sisters", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "sisters", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.053004116, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "house", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "house", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.053004116, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "mother", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "mother", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.041229423, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "brother", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "brother", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.026382832, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "owner", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "owner", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "Color3": 0, 
    "Color2": 7, 
    "categories": [], 
    "Gender": 2, 
    "Age": 3, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "FurLength": 1, 
    "Quantity": 1, 
    "language": "en", 
    "Vaccinated": 2, 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 0.3, 
        "score": 0.3
    }, 
    "Sterilized": 2
}