{
    "Fee": 0, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "THERE ARE FOUR KITTENS GINGER, BLACKIE, SILVER, TUTU THE MOTHER IS A PART SIAMESE LILAC POINT I LIVE IN A CONDO AND I HAVE TO FIND HOMES FOR THE KITTENS WELL FED, CLEAN AND VERY LIVELY AND LOVABLE I AM MAGGIE, TEL KL AMPANG HILIR,", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }
    ], 
    "PhotoAmt": 0.0, 
    "Breed1": 25, 
    "Breed2": 0, 
    "MaturitySize": 2, 
    "Dewormed": 2, 
    "label": 4, 
    "Color1": 1, 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.2243524, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "MOTHER", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }, 
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "TUTU", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "TUTU", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.21995294, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "KITTENS GINGER", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "KITTENS GINGER", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.13533202, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "BLACKIE", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "BLACKIE", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.086420216, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "HOMES", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "HOMES", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.076745406, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "SIAMESE LILAC POINT", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "SIAMESE LILAC POINT", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.06116524, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "CONDO", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "CONDO", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0604365, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "PART", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "PART", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.053125817, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "SILVER", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "SILVER", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.025375586, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "MAGGIE", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "MAGGIE", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0h36rz5", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maggie_Greene"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.021467103, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "KITTENS", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "KITTENS", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.01781338, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "AMPANG HILIR", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "AMPANG HILIR", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.01781338, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "TEL", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "TEL", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "Color3": 6, 
    "Color2": 3, 
    "categories": [], 
    "Gender": 3, 
    "Age": 3, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "FurLength": 1, 
    "Quantity": 2, 
    "language": "en", 
    "Vaccinated": 2, 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 0.2, 
        "score": 0.2
    }, 
    "Sterilized": 2
}