{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 1, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.5127571, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "friend", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "friend", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.27847722, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "message", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "message", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.10766055, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.042333078, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "kitten", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "kitten", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.026089821, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.013383943, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0076090256, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Dataran Prima", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "Dataran Prima", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.007059504, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0023148789, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Taman Ikan Emas", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Taman Ikan Emas", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0023148789, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Cheras", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Cheras", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/09z0md", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cheras,_Kuala_Lumpur"
            }
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 1, 
        "score": 0.3
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "My friend found this kitten, that's his message: This small kitten is looking for a home.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "I found him today at Dataran Prima and brought him home with me to Taman Ikan Emas, Cheras.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": 0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Please, call if you would like to give him home.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}