{
    "Fee": 0, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Harry, Louie and Clare are still up for adoption, George is with someone.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "These babies are completely homeless and are being fed but no home...", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.4, 
                "score": -0.4
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "They really need a home please give them yours and you will have their hearts furever...", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.1, 
                "score": 0.1
            }
        }
    ], 
    "PhotoAmt": 1.0, 
    "Breed1": 307, 
    "Breed2": 141, 
    "MaturitySize": 2, 
    "Dewormed": 3, 
    "label": 3, 
    "Color1": 1, 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.25569233, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "babies", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "babies", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.15014613, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Louie", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Louie", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.15014613, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Clare", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Clare", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.14673452, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Harry", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Harry", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.09846077, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "adoption", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "adoption", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.07087743, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "George", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "George", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.06736174, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "someone", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "someone", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.034668837, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.016101843, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "hearts", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "hearts", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0098102605, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "Color3": 0, 
    "Color2": 2, 
    "categories": [], 
    "Gender": 3, 
    "Age": 3, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "FurLength": 1, 
    "Quantity": 3, 
    "language": "en", 
    "Vaccinated": 3, 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 0.5, 
        "score": 0
    }, 
    "Sterilized": 3
}