{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 3, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.5040603, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "pups", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "pups", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.20441754, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "sisters", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "sisters", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.123553865, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Muffin", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "Muffin", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/01tcjp", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muffin"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.056720145, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "mother", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "mother", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.025685955, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "food", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "food", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.024946066, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "siblings", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "siblings", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0191463, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Melody", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Melody", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.01351051, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "homes", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "homes", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0114605175, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Minnie", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Minnie", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0k5mc", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Minnie_Mouse"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0114605175, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Marie", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Marie", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.005038242, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Maggie", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Maggie", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 1.6, 
        "score": 0.3
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Muffin and her five sisters are cute pups, abandoned by their mother.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.1, 
                "score": -0.1
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "They have been weaned and put on softened solid food.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.5, 
                "score": 0.5
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Her siblings are Melody, Maggie, May, Minnie and Marie.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Looking for good, loving homes.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.9, 
                "score": 0.9
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}