{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 2, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.7349777, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "boy", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "boy", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.11241674, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Thunder", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }, 
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Thunder", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Thunder", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0ngt1", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thunder"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.05842671, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "home", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "home", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.019707384, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "road", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "road", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.019707384, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "cars", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "CONSUMER_GOOD", 
            "name": "cars", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.019469691, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "brother", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "brother", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.018012775, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "rescuer", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "rescuer", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0059995493, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "pups", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "pups", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0056410288, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "vignes", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "vignes", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.0056410288, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Catherine", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Catherine", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 2, 
        "score": 0.5
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Thunder is a handsome and loving boy looking for a furever home .", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.9, 
                "score": 0.9
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "He and his brother were left alone on the road almost knocked down by cars.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Thankfully enough our rescuer manage to rescue the pups in time.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.5, 
                "score": 0.5
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "If your interested in adopting Thunder please call (vignes) or (Catherine) .", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}