{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 4, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.3242042, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "girl", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "girl", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.21279638, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Molly", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Molly", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.16515495, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Character", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }, 
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "girl", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Character", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.114913814, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "owner", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "owner", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.057959788, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "vaccine", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "vaccine", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.04452172, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "homes", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "homes", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.027449502, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "street", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "street", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.023216525, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Shy", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "ORGANIZATION", 
            "name": "Shy", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.019268265, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "call", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "call", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.010514861, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "homes", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "homes", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 2.4, 
        "score": 0.6
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Molly is behave good and polite girl.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": 0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Healthy &amp; vaccine.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.5, 
                "score": 0.5
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Looking for lovely forever homes.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.8, 
                "score": 0.8
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Character: Shy girl but easily attached when get close If you are committed owner, please come and give them a homes before they are being release to street on 11/3/17(final call)", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.2, 
                "score": 0.2
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}