{
    "language": "en", 
    "label": 3, 
    "tokens": [], 
    "entities": [
        {
            "salience": 0.6846375, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Bailey", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Bailey", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.10600258, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "others", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "others", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.102704704, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "hills", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "hills", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.025393665, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Taman Melawati", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "PROPER"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "LOCATION", 
            "name": "Taman Melawati", 
            "metadata": {
                "mid": "/m/0c2j7g", 
                "wikipedia_url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taman_Melawati"
            }
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.01614194, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "children", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "children", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.014027462, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "people", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "people", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.012974623, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "health", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "health", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.012974623, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "sound temperament", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "OTHER", 
            "name": "sound temperament", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.011106783, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "children", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "children", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.009738541, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "Adopters", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "Adopters", 
            "metadata": {}
        }, 
        {
            "salience": 0.004297609, 
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "text": {
                        "content": "family", 
                        "beginOffset": -1
                    }, 
                    "type": "COMMON"
                }
            ], 
            "type": "PERSON", 
            "name": "family", 
            "metadata": {}
        }
    ], 
    "documentSentiment": {
        "magnitude": 2.8, 
        "score": 0.4
    }, 
    "sentences": [
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Bailey, like many others before him, was dumped in the hills that surround Taman Melawati.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.3, 
                "score": -0.3
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "He is very fond of people and adores children.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.8, 
                "score": 0.8
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "He seems to be in good health and sound temperament.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": 0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "We really hope he will be adopted quickly by a family with gentle children.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.7, 
                "score": 0.7
            }
        }, 
        {
            "text": {
                "content": "Adopters must agree to desex him when he is old enough.", 
                "beginOffset": -1
            }, 
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0, 
                "score": 0
            }
        }
    ], 
    "categories": []
}